J. Gus Liebenow Collection, 1882-2011 LCP2007/02
Liberian Collections
- Outside Organizations
  - Midwest Political Science Association,, undated, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    includes one oversized item not found in folder
  - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
  - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities,, undated, 1983-1991 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous Organizations, undated, 1982-1994 (Box 10)
  - Moran, Stahl and Boyer (consulting), undated, 1980-1984 (Box 10)
  - Mozambique Education Fund, Inc., undated, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Multinational Strategies, Inc., 1984 (Box 10)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities,, undated, 1978-1992 (Box 10)
  - Newsletters
    - "Africa Watch", 1990-1994 (Box 10)
    - "Liberia Today", 1991 (Box 10)
    - "Liberian Diaspora", 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - "The Liberian Voice", 1993-1994 (Box 10)
    - "Lofaland", 1986-1993 (Box 10)
      Oversized
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1986-1996 (Box 10)
    - "Negarit Gazeta" (Ethiopia), 1975 (oversize) (Box 10)
  - Other Universities and Colleges
    - Ahmadu Bello University,, undated, 1962-1968 (Box 10)
    - Butler University,, undated, 1989 (Box 10)
    - Duke University,, undated, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - Fourah Bay University, 1965-1966 (Box 10)
    - Georgetown University, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
    - Harvard University,, undated, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Harvard University – J. Gus Liebenow Fellowship, 1952-1956 (Box 10)
    - Howard University, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Iowa State University,, undated, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Job Offers from Other Universities, 1957-1966 (Box 10)
    - Job Search Inquiries, 1973-1978 (Box 10)
    - Mary Baldwin College, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Universities/Colleges, undated, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Northwestern University,, undated, 1983-1988 (Box 10)
    - The Ohio State University, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Purdue University,, undated, 1983-1989 (Box 10)
    - St. Joseph's College, undated (Box 10)
    - Temple University, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Universitat Bayreuth, 1987-1989 (Box 10)
    - University of Alabama,, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 10)
    - University of Florida, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
    - University of Illinois,, undated, 1958-1988 (Box 10)
    - University of Notre Dame,, undated, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Oxfam, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Pasitam,, undated, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Rotary Club, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 10)
  - Social Science Research Council - Liebenow Grant,, undated, 1953-1966 (Box 10)
  - Society for the Conservation of Nature in Liberia, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - South African Development Coordination Conference (SADCC)
    - Administrative Information, 1980-1982 (Box 10)
    - Economic Liberation Reports, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Newsclips, undated, 1980-1982 (Box 10)
    - Notes, undated, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Reports, undated, 1981 (Box 10)
    - SADEX, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Statements, Speeches, etc., 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - Special Emergency Life Food Programme, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Union of Liberia Associations in America, Inc., undated, 1987 (Box 11)
  - United Nations Environment Program, undated (Box 11)
  - United States Committee for Refugees, 1992 (Box 11)
  - UNESCO, undated (Box 11)
  - Universities Field Staff International (formely AUFS)
    - Address Lists, 1981-1987 (Box 11)
    - Biographical Information on Liebenow,, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
    - Campus Coordinators, 1984-1987 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, undated, 1979-1986 (Box 11)
    - Finances, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Brown University,, undated, 1981-1985 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: California State University,, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Dow Chemical Company, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Library of International Relations,, Undated, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Michigan State University,, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Southern Center for International Studies,, undated, 1980- 1982 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Standard Oil of Indiana, undated, 1981-1983 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Temple University,, undated, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Alabama-Birmingham,, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Colorado-Boulder,, undated, 1984-1987 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Kansas,, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Missouri-Columbia,, undated, 1982-1987 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Oklahoma,, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Pittsburgh,, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: University of Wisconsin-River Falls, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Lectures and Schedules: Utah State University,, undated, 1980-1985 (Box 11)
    - Map of Tanzania, undated (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous, undated, 1980-1986 (Box 11)
    - Newsletters, 1979-1985 (Box 11)
    - Notes: Human Rights, undated (Box 11)
    - Notes: Marriage and the Family, undated (Box 11)
    - Notes: Politics and Education in Africa, undated (Box 11)
    - Notes: South Africa-The Future of Apartheid, undated (Box 11)
    - Notes: South Africa-Sources of Change,, undated, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Africa: Four Crises of Political Development", 1979 (Box 11)
    - Report: "African Conflict and Superpower Involvement in the Western Indian Ocean", 1980 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Biharzia Control in Swaziland-The Dilemma of Development", 1981 (Box 11)
    - Report: "The Caucus Race: International Conflict in East Africa and the Horn", 1977 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Gaining Political Participation Among Tribal Minorities – The Role of the Party in Tanzania" – draft, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Liberia: The Dissolution of Privilege" parts i-iii, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Liberia: Dr. Doe and the Demise of Democracy", 1984 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Malawi: Clean Water for the Rural Poor", 1981 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Malawi's Search for Food Self-Sufficiency", parts i-iii, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Reports: Miscellaneous, undated, 1980-1984 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Nyerre of Tanzania: The Legend and the Ledger", 1987 (Box 11)
    - Report: "SADCC: Challenging the 'South African Connection' ", 1982 (Box 11)
    - Report: "South Africa: Home 'not-so-sweet" Homelands", 1986 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Southern Africa: Not Yet Quiet on the Western Front", 1989 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Southern African Hegemony part i: South Africa Tightens the Noose", 1984 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Southern African Hegemony part ii: Impact of the Nkomati 'Accord' ", 1984 (Box 11)
    - Report: "Zimbabwe: A Political Balance Sheet", 1981 (Box 11)
    - Schedules and Itineraries, undated, 1980-1987 (Box 11)
    - Suggested Lectures and Reports, 1981-1987 (Box 11)
  - Wright Patterson Contracting Center,, undated, 1983-1987 (Box 11)
- Personal Files
  - 'A', 1972-1987 (Box 11)
  - Abu-Baker, Albadr,, undated, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Alila, Patrick, 1972-1984 (Box 11)
  - Al-Sohaibani, Abdolrahonzan, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Howard,, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Joel,, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Apreala, Felix, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Ardaiolo, Frank P., 1974 (Box 11)
  - 'B', 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Baikie, David Adamu, 1977-1985 (Box 11)
  - Banda, Hastings K., undated (Box 11)
  - Banks, Arthur, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Barkan, Joel, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Bartlett, David,, undated, 1972-1982 (Box 11)
  - Bate, Steve,, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Boeder, Robert,, undated, 1981-1985 (Box 11)
  - Bonser, Charles, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Booker, Judith, undated (Box 11)
  - Bowe, Hilary,, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Boyd, David,, undated, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Bradley, T.C., undated, 1987-1989 (Box 11)
  - Bradley, Walter, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Bravmann, Rene,, undated, 1973-1983 (Box 11)
  - Brempong, Owusu,, undated, 1979-1985 (Box 11)
  - Brokensha, David,, undated, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Brooks, Douglas J.,, undated, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Brooks, George,, undated, 1970-1985 (Box 11)
  - Brown, Ed,, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 11)
  - Buchanan, Carole,, undated, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Buffie, Edward, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Burnett, David, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Byrnes, Robert,, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - 'C', undated, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Callahan, Mary, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Calzaretta, Anthony, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Carleton, Frances, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Carmona, Narciso B.,, undated, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Carter, Gwendolen,, undated, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Carter, Jeanette,, undated, 1981-1984 (Box 12)
  - Chaitin, Gilbert,, undated, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Chiviya, Esau,, undated, 1980-1983 (Box 12)
  - Chiviya, Ivy Hamundidi, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Clark, James, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Cohen, William,, undated, 1974–1979 (Box 12)
  - Collier, John, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Collins, Kevin,, undated, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Comedy, Yolanda, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Condit, Lisa,, undated, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Conners, Michael, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Conteh, Sorie, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Cottingham, Clement, 1976-1980 (Box 12)
  - Crossey, John, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Curtain, Phil/Pat Romero,, undated, 1980-1983 (Box 12)
  - 'D', undated (Box 12)
  - Daehler, Jennifer,, undated, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Daleck, Jacek, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Davis, Gina,, undated, 1989–1990 (Box 12)
  - Davis, James,, undated, 1987 (Box 12)
  - d'Azevedo, Warren,, undated, 1980 (Box 12)
  - DeLancey, Mark,, undated, 1975-1989 (Box 12)
  - DeLancey, Virginia,, undated, 1977–1991 (Box 12)
  - Dewey, Bill, 1983 (Box 12)
  - DeShield, McKinley, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Dhikusoka, Joseph, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Dike, Azuka,, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 12)
  - Dremonas, George,, undated, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Dresel, Roland, 1977-1981 (Box 12)
  - Dumett, Ann Marie,, undated, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Dunn, Elwood,, undated, 1980-1986 (Box 12)
  - 'E', 1983 (Box 12)
  - Ebo, Obi, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Elfenbaum, Michael,, undated, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Elhassan, Elmutasim,, undated, 1986–1987 (Box 12)
  - Elliot, Swanzy, 1980-1983 (Box 12)
  - 'F', 1984 (Box 12)
  - Farias, Tito,, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 12)
  - Fenton, Leslie, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Finch, Jim,, undated, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Fiore, Sharon, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Fleetwood, Rick,, undated, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Flint, Mike, 1988–1989 (Box 12)
  - Ford, Jennifer, 1983–1984 (Box 12)
  - Ford, Martin,, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Forh, Cyrenius,, undated, 1975-1982 (Box 12)
  - Franda, Marcus,, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 12)
  - Fulton, Richard, 1978 (Box 12)
  - 'G', 1982-1989 (Box 12)
  - Gallimore, Timothy,, undated, 1983-1988 (Box 12)
  - Gaskins, John, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Gellar, Sheldon,, undated, 1977–1985 (Box 12)
  - Geoffrion, Charles,, undated, 1973-1981 (Box 12)
  - Gertz, Michael,, undated, 1980–1985 (Box 12)
  - Gharib, Clint,, undated, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Ginther, Diane,, undated, 1988–1989 (Box 12)
  - Girdner, Janet, 1979–1980 (Box 12)
  - Glover, Arthur, 1979-1981 (Box 12)
  - Goble, Willis,, undated, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Goldman, Etel,, undated, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Gordon, Troy W.,, undated, 1980–1984 (Box 12)
  - Gosebrink, Jean,, undated, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Green, Daniel,, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 12)
  - Greenstein, Lewis,, undated, 1975-1980 (Box 12)
  - Greiner, Matthew,, undated, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Groeslsema, Robert,, undated, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Gugler, Josef, undated (Box 12)
  - Guthrie, Charles, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
  - 'H', 1982-1988 (Box 12)
  - Halisi, C.R.D.,, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 12)
  - Hansen, Emmanuel,, undated, 1977-1988 (Box 12)
  - Harris, John,, undated, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Hartwig, Gerald, 1975-1985 (Box 12)
  - Haugh, Mary, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - Healey, Robert,, undated, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Herman, Pamela,, undated, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Hershfield, Allan, 1974-1987 (Box 12)
  - Hlophe, Stephen,, undated, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
  - Hodge, Carlton, undated (Box 12)
  - Hopkins, Barbara,, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 12)
  - Howell, Dan,, undated, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Hunter, John,, undated, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Hyneman, Charles,, undated, 1958-1989 (Box 12)
  - 'I', 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - 'J', 1980-1988 (Box 13)
  - Jackson, Carl, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - Janda, Kenneth, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Kaba, Lansine,, undated, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Kanno, Ayalew, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Kante, Mamadou,, undated, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Karp, Ivan,, undated, 1975-1988 (Box 13)
  - Keim, Curtis, 1978-1982 (Box 13)
  - Kellar, Edmond,, undated, 1975-1979 (Box 13)
  - Kim, Kwan, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Konuwa, Alfred B.,, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - Knoll, Arthur,, undated, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Kramer, David,, undated, 1975-1987 (Box 13)
  - Lambert, Louis (Scrappy),, undated, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Laves, Walter, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Leighton, Neil,, undated, 1976-1987 (Box 13)
  - Leopold, Robert,, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Loescher, Samuel, 1975-1980 (Box 13)
  - Lofchie, Michael, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Lucas, John,, undated, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
  - Luneburg, Robert,, undated, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Lundgard, Joan, 1983 (Box 13)
  - 'M', undated, 1975-1982 (Box 13)
  - McCormick, John,, undated, 1987-1991 (Box 13)
  - McHenry, Dean,, undated, 1976-1990 (Box 13)
  - Malik, Barry,, undated, 1969-1984 (Box 13)
  - Martin, Phyllis, 1978-1981 (Box 13)
  - Martin, Richard, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Masaya, T.R, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Massey, Michael, 1982-1989 (Box 13)
  - Massing, Andreas,, undated, 1973-1988 (Box 13)
  - Matiko, Julius,, undated, 1973-1987 (Box 13)
  - Mato, Akume,, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Mawaya, Anthony,, undated, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Miller, David, undated (Box 13)
  - Miller, Norman,, undated, 1981-1990 (Box 13)
  - Morgan, E. Philip, 1971-1982 (Box 13)
  - Mukete, Abel, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Munger, David, 1976 (Box 13)
  - 'N', undated, 1976-1981 (Box 13)
  - Nava, Julian, 1984-1988 (Box 13)
  - Neher, William,, undated, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Newmann, David,, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 13)
  - Nimtz, August,, undated, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
  - Njisane, Mlaheni,, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - Nyerere, Julius K., 1971 (Box 13)
  - 'O', 1990 (Box 13)
  - O'Connor, James, 1983 (Box 13)
  - O'Meara, Patrick,, undated, 1980-1988 (Box 13)
  - O'Toole, Thomas,, undated, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Ogundimu, Folu,, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - Olorunsola, Victor,, undated, 1976-1990 (Box 13)
  - 'P', undated, 1977-1984 (Box 13)
  - Paden, John,, undated, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Page, Cindy,, undated, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Patterson, Craig, 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Peel, John D.Y .,, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 13)
  - Perinbaum, B. Marie,, undated, 1974-1979 (Box 13)
  - Polk, James,, undated, 1980-1983 (Box 13)
  - Rai, Abel, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Reed, Cyrus,, undated, 1980-1987 (Box 13)
  - Robertson, Claire,, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Romero, Patricia, 1979-1988 (Box 13)
  - Ronen, Dov, 1976-1985 (Box 13)
  - Rosberg, Carl G.,, undated, 1977-1985 (Box 13)
  - 'S', undated, 1975-1988 (Box 14)
  - Samkange, Tommie, 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Sample, Ward, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Sawyer, Amos,, undated, 1980-1989 (Box 14)
  - Schrag, Norman,, undated, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
  - Segal, Ed,, undated, 1976-1982 (Box 14)
  - Seyon, Patrick,, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 14)
  - Shaw, Tim,, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Siegmann, William,, undated, 1975-1988 (Box 14)
  - Simpson, Dick, undated (Box 14)
  - Skylar, Richard,, undated, 1975-1981 (Box 14)
  - Smith, Robert S., 1982 (Box 14)
  - Smith, Stewart, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
  - Smithburn, J. Eric, 1975-1980 (Box 14)
  - Snipe, Tracy, 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Soderlund, Dorothy,, undated, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Stanley, Nzefeh,, undated, 1981-1983 (Box 14)
  - Stewart, Peter, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Stockton, Rex,, undated, 1977-1985 (Box 14)
  - Stone, Ruth, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Stryker, Richard, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Stulz, Newell M., 1983-1988 (Box 14)
  - Sturnfield, James, 1987 (Box 14)
  - 'T', 1977-1979 (Box 14)
  - Thomson, James,, undated, 1975-1980 (Box 14)
  - Thornton, Dennis,, undated, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Toler, Deborah,, undated, 1975-1981 (Box 14)
  - Tweh, John,, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - [Unknown Last Name], Deb, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Utomi, Patrick,, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - Vaughan, James,, undated, 1978-1991 (Box 14)
  - Viecelli, Jackie,, undated, 1974-1989 (Box 14)
  - VonGnielinski, Stefan,, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 14)
  - 'W', 1986 (Box 14)
  - Warren, D. Michael,, undated, 1971-1988 (Box 14)
  - Washington, Charles,, undated, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Weisel, William,, undated, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Wilkins, Philip,, undated, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Williams, T. Nelson,, undated, 1983-1990 (Box 14)
  - Wilke, Ekkehare-teja,, undated, 1972-1985 (Box 14)
  - Wilson, George M., 1975 (Box 14)
  - Wolpe, Howard, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Wunsch, James S.,, undated, 1976-1984 (Box 14)
  - Wynne, Susan, 1976-1988 (Box 14)
  - Yeager, Rodger,, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Yoder, David, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Young, Crawford, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Young, Roland,, undated, 1978 (Box 14)
  - 'Z', 1965 (Box 14)
- Subject Files
  - Africa – Articles and Clippings, 1961-2011 (Box 14)
  - African Brochures, undated (Box 14)
  - African Journal Articles, undated, 1907-1966 (Box 14)
  - Biographical Information
    - Articles about Liebenow,, undated, 1960-2009 (Box 14)
    - Biographical Sketches and Related Documents, undated, 1975-1989 (Box 14)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1980-1990 (Box 14)
    - J. Gus Liebenow Memorial Speeches and Memorabilia, 1993-2001 (Box 14)
    - Publications of J. Gus Liebenow, 1980, 1989, undated (Box 14)
  - Brochures – Indiana University and Bloomington, undated (Box 15)
  - China Memorabilia, undated (Box 15)
  - Ephemera, undated, 1999 (Box 15)
  - Indiana University Liberian Collections Project, undated (Box 15)
  - Liberia, 1958-2000 (Box 15)
  - Liberian Officials, 1972 (Box 15)
    (oversize)
  - Liberian Updates, 1994 (Box 15)
  - List of Names, undated (Box 15)
  - Makua Tribe, undated, 1882-1965 (Box 15)
  - Malawi – Clippings and Contacts,, undated, 1978-1994 (Box 15)
  - Maps of Monrovia, undated (Box 15)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous Liebenow Notes, undated (Box 15)
  - News Clippings, undatd, 1944-1995 (Box 15)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 15)
  - Pamphlets and Programs, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 15)
  - Permits and Certificates, undated, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Photographs, undated, 1976-1990 (Box 15)
  - Photographs - Liebenow, 1989-1993 (Box 15)
  - Photographs – Malawi,, undated, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Photographs – Zimbabwe, undated (Box 15)
  - Presidential Messages – Liberia, 1903-1960 (Box 15)
  - "The Secretariat" (Tanzania), 1956 (Box 15)
  - Speech – "Freedom to Choose" – High School Commencement, 1973 (Box 15)
  - TANU Publications, 1967 (Box 15)
- Writings
  - Book Reviews
    - "African Politics: Crises and Challenges",, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 15)
    - "Behavioral Syndromes and Recruitment Patterns of Liberian District Commissioners, Pre- 1964 ,", 1975 (Box 15)
    - "Colonial Rule and Political Development in Tanzania",, undated, 1972 (Box 15)
    - "Liberia: The Evolution of Privilege",, undated, 1969-1974 (Box 15)
    - "Liberia: The Quest for Democracy",, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, undated, 1970-1988 (Box 15)
  - Conference Papers
    - "Africa's Challenge to America", 1959 (Box 15)
    - "Food Self-Sufficiency in Malawi: Are Successes Transferable?", 1985 (Box 15)
    - "Malawi: Strategies for the Attainment of Self-Sufficiency in Food And the Strengthening of the Smallholder Sector", 1981 (Box 15)
    - "Regional Integration in Africa: Reflections on Problems and Prospects", 1988 (Box 15)
  - Drafts
    - "Africa's Place In The Sun",, undated, 1985 (Box 15)
    - "American Policy in Africa: The Reagan Years", 1982 (Box 15)
    - "Behavioral Syndromes and Recruitment Patterns of Liberian District Commissioners, Pre- 1964 ", 1975 (Box 15)
    - "The Central African Federation: An Analysis of the Bases of Opposing Attitudes", 1951 (Box 15)
    - "Droughts, Dams, and Development: A Study of Water Resources Policies And Planning in Sub-Saharan Africa", undated (Box 15)
    - "Food Self-Sufficiency in Malawi: Are Successes Transferable?", 1986 (Box 15)
    - "Liberia: The Special Relationship with the U.S.A.", 1992-1994 (Box 15)
    - "The Military Factor in African Politics: A 25 Year Perspective", 1984 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Drafts, undated (Box 15)
    - "Native Authority System", undated (Box 15)
    - "Nyerre of Tanzania: Part 1, The Legend and the Ledger", undated (Box 15)
    - "Prospects for Political Democracy in West Africa", undated (Box 15)
    - "The Quest for East African Unity: 'One Step Forward, Two Steps Backward' ", 1977 (Box 16)
    - "The Republic of Liberia", 1962 (Box 16)
    - "A Select Bibliography on Liberia", undated (Box 16)
    - "Some Problems in Introducing Local Government Reform in Tanganyika", undated (Box 16)
    - "Southern Africa: Not Quiet on the Western Front", 1988 (Box 16)
    - "Tribalism, Traditionalism and Modernism in Chagga Local Government", undated, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Other Writing Projects
    - "A War Without Purpose in a Country Without Identity",, undated, 1995 (Box 16)
    - "Adapting the Cabinet Secretariat to American Needs", undated (Box 16)
    - "African One-Party States" Correspondence, etc.,, undated, 1961-1963 (Box 16)
    - Bibliographiesundated, 1969 (Box 16)
    - "Book of Knowledge" – Liberia,, undated, 1963-1978 (Box 16)
    - "Central-Local Elite Relationships in the Nation-Building Process in East Africa", undated (Box 16)
    - "China 1983" undated (Box 16)
    - "Country Orientation Notebook for Africa",, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
    - Dissertation Drafts and Notes, undated, 1955 (Box 16)
    - Dissertation Drafts and Notes, undated (Box 16)
    - Dissertation Proposal, undated, 1953 (Box 16)
    - "Exploring Healing", 1991 (Box 16)
    - "The Final Days of Dr. Doe", 1992 (Box 16)
    - "Fragments of Marseilles" In Tempo, 1949 (Box 16)
    - "Journal of African Administration" – Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 16)
    - "Kinship, Achievement and Social Change in Tribal Societies", 1970 (Box 16)
    - "Language in Liberia in the 19th Century: The Settlers' Perspective", 1981 (Box 16)
    - Liberia Articles, undated, 1970-1996 (Box 16)
    - "Liberia: The Quest for Democracy" - Art, 1991 (Box 16)
    - Lists, Tables, Maps –Liberia and the people, undated (Box 16)
    - Livingston, William,, undated, 1959-1963 (Box 16)
    - Manuscript Consulting, undated, 1976-1980 (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, undated (Box 16)
    - Notes for Malawi Articles, undated (Box 16)
    - Notes on Vai Script, undated (Box 16)
    - "Patterns of Authority in West Africa", 1951 (Box 16)
    - "Prescriptive Alliance and Ritual Collaboration in Loma Society", 1991 (Box 16)
    - Photocopies of 19th Century Articles, undated (Box 16)
    - Poems, undated (Box 16)
    - "The Rainstick", 1991 (Box 16)
    - "Rebel Destinies: Remembering Herskovits Autobiographically", 1991 (Box 16)
    - "Rehabilitation and Reconstruction in Liberia", 1993 (Box 16)
    - Reviews (not Liebenow), undated, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
    - "Social Impact of Liberia's Civil War" – proposal, undated (Box 16)
    - Somalian Refuges Articles,, undated, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
    - "Some Aspects of Nyamwezi Witch Belief", undated (Box 16)
    - "Some Note on Krahn Culture" undated (Box 16)
    - South African News Articles,, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 16)
    - Tanganyika Notes and Documents, 1953-1966, undated (Box 16)
    - Tanganyika Photocopied Articles,, undated, 1937-1960 (Box 17)
    - Tanzania,, undated, 1955-1968 (Box 17)
    - "Toward a Typology of Nation Building in New States of Africa", undated (Box 17)
    - "Traditional History and Social Structure in Ufipa", 1964 (Box 17)